Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents 5718
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents
1881-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC)
5718
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5698408
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5718 mf: Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents on Microfilm 5818 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 662 (Mt. Morris, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5822 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Rochester, NY. Records on Microfilm 5810: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records on Microfilm 5819 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1508 (Lyons, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5820 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5828: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books 5828 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5826: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books 5826 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5817 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5827: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books 5827 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books on Microfilm 5686 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners. Local 187 (Geneva, NY) Records on Microfilm
Carpenters--Labor unions--United States.; Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (U.S.)
5698408
- Correspondence w/ AFL, 1903-1911 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence w/ Building Trades Dpt. Of AFL, 1911-1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence, 1916-1922 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence of Frank Duffy, General Secretary, 1906-1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence of Frank Duffy, General Secretary (cont.), 1928-1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence of Frank Duffy, General Secretary (cont.), 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence of Samuel Gompers, AFL President, 1901-1906 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence, 1957-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence of P.J. McGuire, General Secretary, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence of P.J. McGuire, General Secretary (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Testimony of PJ McGuire, General Secretary, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Documents of PJ McGuire, General Secretary, 1883-1906 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Union History, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Union History (cont.), 1905 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Union History (cont.), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Union History (cont.), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Union History (cont.), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Union History (cont.), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Union History (cont.), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Historic Documents, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Scope and Contents
  By-laws, rosters
- Union History (cont.), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- History of Union in NYC (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Union History, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Testimonial by President Emeritus William Hutcheson, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Union Publications (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Union Publications (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Union Publications, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Union Publications (cont.), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- "The World of PJ McGuire: A Study of the American Labor Movement", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  PhD Dissertation
- Union Publications (Box 1, Folder 30)
- "History of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America," Part 1, 1881-1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  By Frank Duffy, General Secretary
- "History of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America" Part 2`, 1881-1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)